Zoltuya Anhbayr

<u>Front-End Developer</u> I am a front-end developer with more than 2 years of experience writing html, css, and next js, react js. I'm motivated, result-focused and seeking a successful team-oriented company with opportunity to grow.

Ulaanbatar, Mongolia, (+976) 95088118 neodev0725@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

ICT GROUP, Ulaanbaatar — Front-end Developer

MAR 2022 - Sep 2022

- Developed functional and appealing web applications based on usability, resulting in increased customer satisfaction.
- Developed custom themes for popular CMS platforms like WordPress or Drupal as per client specifications.
- Utilized version control systems such as Git to track changes throughout the development process.

Tech Pack, Ulaanbaatar — Software Tester

JUNE 2023 - AUG 2023

- Improved software quality by executing thorough test cases and identifying critical defects.
- Conducted comprehensive security tests on applications to identify vulnerabilities, safeguarding sensitive customer data from potential breaches.

INDRA CYBER INSTITUTE, Ulaanbaatar — Programist

NOV 2023 - JAN 2024

 Developed functional and appealing web applications based on usability, resulting in increased customer satisfaction.

EDUCATION

6 high scgool, Ulaanbaatar — High School Diploma

Sep 2007 - June 2018

HIGH SCHOOL GRADED

University of the Humanities, Ulaanbaatar — Bachelor

Sep 2018 - June 2022

Bachelor of Science

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, TAILWIND
- React JS, NEXT JS, Javascript
- MongoDB, DJANGO
- My Sql, Heidi SQL

AWARDS

CISCO NETWORK
CERTIFICATE - 2020

REACT JS ONLINE CERTIFICATE - 2022

DJANGO META CERTIFICATE
- 2023

LANGUAGES

MONGOLIAN AND ENGLISH